Contact

Tunis-montfleury +21653573786 (Mobile)

abdoumed46574423@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/djeibaba

abdellahi-142968235-abdellahi-

(LinkedIn)

Top Skills machine learning

Deep learning

Mobile Applications
Web Applications

API Development

Languages

Français (Full Professional)

Anglais (Full Professional)

Arabe (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Big Data Vs Data Science

Internet of Things (IoT): Fundamental Course (101 level)

Web Development Bootcamp

Big Data Programming Languages &

Data Analytics, Storage, Mining & Visual Big Data Technologies

AutoML Automated Machine Learning BootCamp (No Code ML)

python programming

Djeibaba Abdellahi

Advanced Technology Engineer

Grand Tunis Metropolitan Area

Summary

I specialize in advanced technology, particularly in AI data processing, with a strong focus on emerging technologies such as smart grids, AI analysis, IoT, machine learning, deep learning, computer vision, and NLP.

You can find detailed descriptions of real projects I have undertaken on my GitHub: https://github.com/khayidjeibab?tab=repositories

Experience

Groupe SFM

Al Software Engineer

February 2024 - Julie 2024 (4 monthes)

Gouvernorat Tunis, Tunisie

Engineering Internship

Energy Disaggregation Based on Unsupervised Learning (Detection of Active or Inactive Electrical Appliances from Their Electrical Signatures Using Unsupervised Learning).

Groupe SFM

Electronics and Automation Specialist February 2023 - August 2023 (7 months)

Gouvernorat Tunis, Tunisie

* Professional Master's Degree Internship*

Design and Implementation of an Autonomous Smart Home with Camera Surveillance (AI & IOT)

SOMELEC

Software Application Engineer April 2021 - July 2021 (4 months)

Nouakchott, Mauritania

Bachelor's Thesis Internship

Development of an API interface for managing a solar park connected to the grid

IBS

Wep developper September 2019 - December 2019 (4 months) Mauritania

volunteer internship

Development of mobile applications for publishing the company's products

Education

Higher School of Engineering in Tunis

Engineering, Advanced Technology · (September 2022 - July 2024)

Université Tunis Carthage

Master's degree, Electronics, Electrical, and Automation · (September 2021 - May 2023)

University of Nouakchott Al Aasriya

Bachelor's Degree, advanced technology Systems · (September 2019 - 2021)